### **JORGE SARRICOLEA VEYRO**

Full-Stack developer with 3 years of hands-on experience, deeply passionate about technology and constantly learning with the latest innovations.











### **About me**

3 years ago, I embarked on my journey in web development, creating attractive and functional web applications. My focus is on merging technical skills with a keen eye for design, which drives me to constantly advance. I firmly believe that true changes requires order, discipline, and perseverance, which are essential for achieving success.

### **Experience**

### **Full-Stack Developer**

**Rocket Code | Full Time** 

July 2024 - Present

Remote

My main role as a Full-Stack Developer with a primary focus on front-end development using Angular and React (JavaScript) and back-end development with Java SpringBoot and Maven. I am responsible for developing tickets according to the project I am assigned to, as the company rotates projects based on taglds.

# Front-End Developer

La DAO | Freelance

May 2024 - August 2024 • 3 months

Remote

My main role as a Front-End Developer, developing the entire interface from scratch for an application to perform transactions on a new smart contract that includes a new cryptocurrency called XOC. Additionally, I was responsible for making pull requests (PR) and resolving merge conflicts as needed.

# **Django Developer**

C

Seguros Gutierrez y Arredondo | Freelance

March 2024 - May 2024 • 2 months

Hibryd

I developed a data retrieval form using Django and PostgreSQL to streamline the prospect acquisition process and enhance efficiency for the recruitment team. Focus was on seamlessly capturing and storing prospect data to optimize lead management.

### **Full-Stack Developer**

### ICCBR 2024 | Freelance

July 2023 - March 2024 • 8 months

Remote

I collaborated in a team to refactor the entire platform, transitioning from PHP to Astro + JavaScript to remove vulnerabilities. My primary focus included building a robust RESTful API for payment processing and email notifications for ticket purchases. Additionally, I contributed to frontend improvements by refactoring and creating UI components.

## **Bubble Developer**

### **Datamatic Software | Full Time**

May 2022 - June 2022 • 1 month

On-site

I was tasked with specific responsibilities across various projects. This included bug fixing, enhancing user interfaces, improving back-end workflows, and updating APIs consumed by each project.

# **Bubble Developer**

ď

### Jumwork | Full Time

June 2020 - January 2022 • 1 year 7 months

Remote

I worked on developing the platform from scratch. This platform is a marketplace with an integrated chat, auction system, email notifications, and a payment gateway via Stripe. My primary goal was to work on all modules to deliver a functional, responsive platform without any development errors.

### **Education**

Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida | 2020 - 2024

Computer Stystems Engineer

### **Main Stack**

JavaScript, TypeScript, Next.Js, React.Js, Astro, TailwindCSS, Node.Js, Express, Prisma, AWS,

### **Skills**

Angular, SpringBoot, Maven, Scaffold, Wagmi, Three.Js, Django, PostgreSQL, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git, PHP, Java, Python, JQuery, Bubble,